Guide to the Alison Lurie papers, [ca. 1960-2013]
Lurie, Alison papers, [ca. 1960-2013]
- Series IV. Miscellaneous
  - Foundation Agenda 1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Notes - Island Story, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Notes, Ideas 1973 -->, 1973-1979 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Acquaintances (Jr Bazaar), 1947-08 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Garland Press, 1974-1976, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, advertisement booklet for Classics of Children's Literature: 1621-1932
  - Clever Gretchen, Reviews, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Bestiary, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Illustrations
  - National Book Award, 1979-04-1979-11 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Published Articles - General, Typescripts to 1989, 1970-1988, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Published Articles to 1989, 1966-1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    Steve Poleskie: Artflyer
  - Articles, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Articles, Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Published Articles, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Radcliffe College Alumnae Recognition Award, 1987-06 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Art (to 1990), 1949-1955, 1969-1975, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Published Articles: Travel Art, 1983-1991, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Interviews, Articles, 1974-1987, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Cornell-related articles
  - Barbara Epstein, 1995, 2006, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Published Article in The New ReviewVol 1 No 2, 1974-05 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 2 copies of poster for Women and Ghosts (Map-case Folder 1)
- Series V. Photographs
  - Alison Lurie, ages 1-16 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Alison Lurie, publicity photos and misc. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of A. L.'s students, 1976-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Imaginary Friends, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Series VI. Cornell Material
  - Cornell - Correspondence, 1968-2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Class Photos, 1971-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    One unlabeled photo
  - Undergraduate Class Photos, 1978-1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    No 1982, no 1987
  - Undergraduate Class Photos, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    No 1994
  - Undergraduate Class Photos, 1996-2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    No 1999, 2001
  - Undergraduate Class Photos, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Box of Student Names (A - G), Undated (Box 18)
    Index cards
  - Box of Student Names (H - R), Undated (Box 18)
  - Box of Student Names (S - Z), Undated (Box 18)
  - Student papers with Lurie's sketches of students, 1983-2003 (Box 19)
    Access restrictions apply.